So again we achieved a lot over the last lectures.
Wic znowu osignlimy wiele podczas ostatnich wykadw.
We have our orders page finished,
Skoczylimy nasz stron zamwie, Mamy naszego
We have our burger builder which is really working great, which leads us forward to the checkout page
producenta burgerw, ktry naprawd dziaa wietnie, ktry prowadzi nas do strony kasy, gdzie
where we load the checkout form, the form here isn't finished but we can issue an order, we are redirected
adujemy formularz kasy, formularz tutaj nie jest gotowy, ale moemy wyda zamwienie,
thereafter and we can see that order here,
jestemy przekierowywani a potem moemy zobaczy t
so that is all working fine.
kolejno tutaj, wic wszystko dziaa dobrze.
Now things we can improve are that
Teraz moemy poprawi ten formularz kasowy,
Checkout form which I just mentioned, this one here
o ktrym wanie wspomniaem, ten tutaj i oczywicie
and of course in general the state management of our application. We can already see that we have to
w oglnoci zarzdzanie pastwem naszej aplikacji. Ju widzimy, e musimy od czasu
use some tricks and workarounds from time to time, that is something we'll improve throughout this course once
do czasu korzysta z niektrych sztuczek i obej, to jest co,
we dive into redux
co poprawimy na tym
though. Still we have a nicely working application which already is way more than just a tiny little
kursie, gdy tylko zanurkujemy w redux. Nadal mamy adnie dziaajc aplikacj, ktra ju jest czym wicej
side project.
ni tylko maym projektem.
Awesome work thus far,
Niesamowita praca do
let's now I'm deeper into forms and then additional features
tej pory, teraz zajmuj si gbszymi formami, a
The react ecosystem offers to us.
nastpnie dodatkowymi funkcjami Reaktywowany ekosystem oferuje nam.